BRAC Additional Records 5735
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BRAC Additional Records
1975-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees (BRAC)
5735
53 cubic feet
53 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3123479
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5488: BRAC Records
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.; Railroads--United States--Employees--Sources.; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
3123479
- Grand Lodge Convention (General), 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  January 1971-April 30, 1975
- 1975 Grand Lodge Convention (General) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  May 1 1975-?
- Resolutions - Receipt Acknowledged (Section 1), 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  1971-March 25, 1975
- Resolutions - Receipt Acknowledged (Section 2), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  March 26, 1975-March 31, 1975
- Resolutions - Receipt Acknowledged (Section 3), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  April 1-3, 1975
- Resolutions: Receipt Acknowledged (Section 4), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  April 4, 1975-April 9, 1975
- Resolutions: Receipt Acknowledged (Section 5), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  April 10, 1975-?
- International President's Staff and Secretaries Attending Convention, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1975 Grand Lodge Convention - System Boards (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Grand Lodge Officers Reports, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1975 Grand Lodge Convention - Foreign Visitors (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1975 Grand Lodge Convention - Transportation (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Washington Hilton Convention Banquet, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Washington Hilton Convention Banquet, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Washington Hilton Convention Banquet, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1975 Grand Lodge Convention - Delegates, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1975 Grand Lodge Convention - Appointments and Committees (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bound Materials and Reports, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Pro-tem Canadian Executive Council, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  September 3, 1975. Bound.
- 1975 Convention - File Copy (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Bound
- 1975 Conventions - Canada, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention (General) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Through March 1979
- Resolutions - Receipt Acknowledged (Section 1), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  1978-March 20, 1979
- Resolutions - Receipt Acknowledged (Section 2), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  March 20, 1979-?
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Local and District Chairman Delegates (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Delegates (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Local Convention Committee (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Committee - The Grand Outer Guard (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Convention Staff (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Honorary Guests and Honorary Visitors (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Banquet (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Finance, Salaries, Mileage, and Per Diem (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - The Grand Sergeant-At-Arms and Assistants (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Tellers Committee (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Credentials (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Delegates-At-Large and Alternatives (Box 4, Folder 8)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Grand Lodge Constitution and Laws (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Retirement, Unemployment Insurance, and Health and Welfare (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on State, Provincial and Federal Legislation (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Appeals (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Official Publication, Printing and Press (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Rules, Order of Business, and Ritual (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - The Grand Chaplain (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Petitions and Resolutions (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 1979 Grand Lodge Convention - The Grand Inner Guard (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Labor Organizations (General), 1963-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  January 1, 1963-August 1973
- Labor Organizations (General), 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  September 1973-November 1979
- Labor Organizations - Air Line Pilots Association, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  July 25, 1972-September 1979
- Labor Organizations - International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Works of America - United Automobile Workers, 1963- 1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  January 1, 1963-September 1979
- Labor Organizations - Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  July 1, 1974-October 1976
- Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  1973-March 1977
- Labor Organizations - Bricklayers, Masons and Plasters International Union, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  January-August 1974
- Labor Organizations - International brotherhood of Carmen, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  1973-August 1978
- Labor Organizations - Retail Clerks International Association, 1960-1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  January 1, 1960-September 1979
- Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  1974-November 1976
- Labor Organizations - American Train Dispatchers Association - Joint Agreement with Order of Railroad Telegraphers (ORT) Covering Union Shop Compliance, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  November 6, 1952
- Labor Organizations - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1944-1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  1944-January 1977
- Labor Organizations - Distillery, Wine, and Allied Workers International Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  February 1978
- Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  1972-February 1975
- Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  1973-September 1978. Includes Bound Materials.
- Labor Organizations - Marine Engineers, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  April 1974
- Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  January 1975
- Labor Organizations - Flight Engineers' International Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  November 7, 1973
- Labor Organizations - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  November 16, 1973
- Labor Organizations - United Garment Workers of America, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  May 1977
- Labor Organizations - American Federation of Government Employees, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  August 1973-April 1974
- Labor Organizations - International Longshoremen's Association, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Labor Organizations - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  1972-December 1979
- Labor Organizations - United Mine Workers of America, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  May 1974
- Labor Organizations - Office Employees International Union, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  January 1, 1955
- Labor Organizations - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  June 1972
- Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Labor Organizations - Railway Employees' Department, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Labor Organizations - Canadian Brotherhood of Railway, Transport, and General Workers, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  January 1, 1960
- Labor Organizations - Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  1972-June 1975
- Labor Organizations - Brotherhood Railroad Signalmen Directory, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Bound. July 1978.
- Labor Organizations - Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1965-1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  January 1, 1965-October 31, 1977
- Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  November 1977-May 1978
- Labor Organizations - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  October 1973-March 1979
- Labor Organizations - United Steelworkers of America, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  1973-February 1978
- Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  1976-October 1978
- Labor Organizations - Railroad Retirement and Railroad Unemployment, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  1972-September 1979
- Labor Organizations - American Federation of Teachers, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  January 1974-February 1979
- Other Organizations - Teamsters (Brotherhood of Railway Carmen versus Teamsters - Pan-American), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1962-1979 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  January 1, 1962-November 1979
- Labor Organizations - Transportation-Communication Division, Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  January 1, 1970-May 1970
- Jurisdiction - Transportation-Communication Employees Union, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  July 1, 1969-June 1973
- Labor Organizations - Textile Workers Union of America, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  1973-August 1976
- Labor Organizations - Theatrical, Stage, and Moving Picture Operators, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  April 1972
- Labor Organizations - United Transportation Union, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  September 1973-June 1979
- Labor Organization - International Typographical Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  February 1973
- Labor Organizations - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  March 1974-May 1978
- Labor Organizations - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  1974-March 1979
- Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  1973-April 1979
- Labor Organizations - Building Service Employees International Union, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Labor Organizations - Transport Workers Union of America, 1960-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  1960-June 1979
- Labor Organizations - Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Association, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Labor Organizations - National Maritime Union, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  1973-June 1976
- Labor Organizations - Communication Workers of America, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  August 1, 1973-October 1979
- Labor Organizations - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Labor Organizations - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  July 1, 1974-May 1978
- Labor Organizations - International Jewelry Workers' Union, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  March 1974-February 1977
- Labor Organizations - International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers Union, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen of North America, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  November 30, 1973- May 1978
- Labor Organizations - Stone Cutters Association of North America, Journeyman, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  October 1974
- Labor Organizations - Utility Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Labor Organizations - International Woodworkers of America, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Labor Organization - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  1973-September 1979
- Labor Organizations - International Association of Fire Fighters, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Labor Organizations - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Labor Organizations - United Farm Workers of America (UFWA), 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  November 28, 1973-July 5, 1979
- Labor Organizations - United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum International Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Labor Organizations - RASSA, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  RASSA?
- Railway Labor Executives Association - General, 1969-1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  August 7, 1969-Nvoember 24, 1976
- Railway Labor Executives Association - General, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  1977-December 1979
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  1977-April 1978
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  1977-February 1979
- Railway Labor Executives Association - News Releases, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Financial Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  1977-July 1978
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Public Relations, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Canada, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Railroad Retirement, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  1978-August 1979
- By-Laws - District Council, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  May 24, 1959
- By-Laws - Greater Detroit District Council, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  January 1972-January 3, 1975
- By-Laws - Chicago District Council, 1961-1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  September 18, 1961; September 1979; December 14, 1979.
- By-Laws - East Saint Louis District Council, 1924-1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  October 22, 1924; June 6, 1975
- By-Laws - Greater New York District Council, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  March 1970; July 28, 1970.
- By-Laws - Association of General Chairmen, 1955-1972 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  September 8, 1955; November 10, 1972.
- By-Laws - Association of General Chairmen, Central of Georgia, 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  December 17, 1957; February 15, 1967.
- By-Laws 0 Association of General Chairmen, Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway, 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  May 22, 1953; August 27, 1957.
- By-Laws - General Chairmen's' Association, Reading Company, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  January 30, 1962; April 10, 1962
- By-Laws - Association of General Chairmen, Southern Railway, 1949-1966 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  April 25, 1949; October 31, 1966
- By-Laws - Association of General Chairmen, Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railway (Rock Island), 1958 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  October 27, 1958
- By-Laws - Association of General Chairmen, Chicago Great Western Railway, 1953-1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  May 11, 1953; January 5, 1965
- By-Laws - General Chairmen's Association, Long Island Railroad, 1956-1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  October 1, 1956; June 1966
- By-Laws - Association of General Chairmen, Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway, 1948-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  March 12, 1948; March 30, 1964
- By-Laws - General Chairmen's Association, Northwest Airlines, 1954-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 7, 1954; April 6, 1966
- Appointments - International President, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  1974-August 31, 1979
- Labor Summit on Inflation, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  September 11, 1974
- Illinois Commerce Commission, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  1973-September 23, 1976
- California Bureau of Labor Statistics - Commissions, State - Railroad, Utility, Labor, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  1976-March 17, 1978
- Iowa Railroad Commission, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- New York State Labor Department, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  1973; May 23, 1977
- Kentucky Department of Labor, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  July 1979
- State Federation of Labor, 1963-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  January 1, 1963-May 10, 1978
- State Federation of Labor - Alabama, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  March 16, 1973-March 23, 1973
- State Federation of Labor - Arkansas, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  June 14, 1973-December 16, 1977
- State Federation of Labor - California, 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  April 21, 1973-September 6, 1979
- State Federation of Labor - Connecticut, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  April 4, 1973-June 8, 1973
- State Federation of Labor - Georgia, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  May 23, 1977
- State Federation of Labor - Illinois, 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  February 26, 1973-March 15, 1979
- State Federation of Labor - Iowa, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  April 18, 1973-May 30, 1975
- State Federation of Labor - Kansas, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  June 1979-August 27, 1979
- State Federation of Labor - Louisiana, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  June 21, 1973
- State Federation of Labor, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  January 14, 1974-June 13, 1975
- State Federation of Labor - Maryland, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  April 28, 1973
- State Federation of Labor - Mississippi, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  August 3, 1972
- State Federation of Labor - Missouri, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  February 1979-April 11, 1979
- State Federation of Labor - Montana, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  September 18, 1972
- State Federation of Labor - Nebraska, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  February 20, 1974
- State Federation of Labor - New Jersey, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  November 12, 1973
- State Federation of Labor - North Carolina, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  September 9, 1975
- State Federation of Labor - Ohio, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  April 10, 1972-September 17, 1976
- State Federation of Labor - South Carolina, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  April 15, 1977
- State Federation of Labor - South Dakota, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  June 21, 1973-February 7, 1975
- State Federation of Labor, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  February 21, 1973-September 26, 1973
- State Federation of Labor - Washington, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  September 17, 1974-November 16, 1979
- State Federation of Labor - West Virginia, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  January 16, 1974
- State Federation of Labor - Wisconsin, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  August 1979
- City Central Bodies, 1963-1979 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  January 1, 1963-February 1979
- Jurisdiction - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1958-1977 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  1958-July 1977
- Jurisdiction - Disputes with Transportation-Communication Employees Union, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  1969-June 1971
- Religious Organizations, 1960-1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  January 1, 1960-March 1974
- Charitable Organizations, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  July 1, 1971-1972
- Charitable Organizations, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  March 1971-September 1974
- Charitable Organizations, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Charitable Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  October 1976-1977
- Charitable Organizations, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Charitable Organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Charitable Organizations - Contributions, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Presented to the Executive Council and Finance Committee February 1972. February 1973.
- Charitable Organizations - Cancer Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  1977-January 1978
- Charitable Organizations - City of Hope, Los Angeles Sanatorium, 1962-1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  January 1, 1962-January 1979
- Charitable Organizations - City of Hope, Los Angeles Sanatorium, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Charitable Organizations - City of Hope - Correspondence with Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Includes Photograph of City of Hope Cardiologist Using Sphygmomanometer recorder. February 16, 1972
- Charitable Organizations - C.L. Dennis Dinner, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Charitable Organizations - Requests for Contribution, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  March 7, 1974
- Charitable Organizations - The United Settlement Appeal, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  1973-November 1974
- Charitable Organizations - United Settlement Appeal, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  August 1974
- Charitable Organizations - Heart Association, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Charitable Organizations - American Red Cross, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Charitable Organizations - New National Foundation (Formerly National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis), 1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  January 1, 1961
- American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  1973-June 1974
- Charitable Organizations - United Settlement Appeal, Chicago, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  1972-October 1974
- Charitable Organizations - Children's Asthma Research Institute and Hospital, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  August 1973
- Charity Organizations - Eugene versus Debs Foundation, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Charitable Organizations - Herbert L. Orlowitz Institute (For the Study of Cancer and Blood Diseases), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  October-November 1979
- Educational Programs - New Direction, Incorporated College Scholarship Program, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Educational Programs - Universities, 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  1973-January 3, 1979
- Educational Programs - Harvard University, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  January 1973-December 1977
- Educational Programs - Term Papers by Students at Harvard, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Educational Programs - Harvard, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  September 1973-June 24, 1974
- Educational Programs - Harvard University, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  January 1978-December 19, 1979
- Educational Programs - Afro-Asian Institute for Labour Studies and Cooperation in Israel, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  August 1973-July 21, 1975
- Educational Programs - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1972-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  1972-January 26, 1979
- Educational Programs - Universities; Labour College of Canada, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  January 16-May 10, 1974
- Educational Programs - Ohio Historical Society, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  1976-October 30, 1978
- International Affairs - General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- International Affairs - General, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  March 1975-December 1978
- International Affairs - General Council of Trade Unions, Japan - White Paper on Wages in 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  May 8, 1974
- International Affairs - Operation Antigua, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  April 7, 1978
- International Affairs - General, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  December 4, 1979
- Asian American Free Labor Institute - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - Operation Brotherhood Statistical Report, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- International Affairs - International Labor Organization, 1965-1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  January 1, 1965-January 11, 1978
- International Affairs - United Nations - United Nations Association of the United States of America; National Citizen's Commission on International Cooperation, 1968- 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  July 1968-January 7, 1977
- International Transport Workers Federation World Congress, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- International Affairs - International Transport Workers Federation, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  November 1974-October 29, 1979
- International Affairs - International Transport Workers Federation, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  June-October 1974
- International Affairs - Foreign Relations, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  January-December 12, 1973
- International Affairs - International Brotherhood Fund, 1966-1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  1966-May 1, 1978